Bethune Theatredanse records, 1957-2012
UCLA Library Special Collections
Bethune Theatredanse records
1957-2012
2304
UCLA Library Special Collections
44.8 linear ft. (17 document boxes, 36 record cartons, and 2 oversize flat boxes)
Materials related to the history and operations of the Bethune Theatredanse dance compnay, and its arts education program Infinite Dreams (formerly known as Dance Outreach), both founded by Zina Bethune. Includes administrative and fundraising records, clippings, photographs, and audio-visual materials documenting Bethune Theatredanse's multi-media productions as well as Dance Outreach activities.
Bethune Theatredanse
Restrictions on Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
COLLECTION CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials in this collection will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. To review these audiovisual materials, you must notify the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk in advance of your visit.
Use of electronic format material requires special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. To review these materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 7992937
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Sean Feeley and Ivy Bethune, 2015.
Biography/History
Zina Bianca Bethune was born in New York City on February 17, 1945, the daughter of Ivy (Vigder) and William Charles Bethune. She started formal ballet training at George Balanchine’s School of American Ballet at six years old. By the age of 14, Bethune was dancing with the New York City Ballet while simultaneously working as an actor, appearing in a variety of television series and movies. Alongside Harvey Keitel, she starred in Martin Scorsese’s first feature film, Who’s That Knocking at My Door, released in 1967. She also reached a wide audience via her role on the CBS TV series The Nurses from 1962-1965. Bethune continued her parallel acting and dancing careers the rest of her life, appearing in several television film and Broadway productions throughout the 1970s-1990s.
Dance became Bethune’s top priority however, and in 1979 she started Zina Bethune and Company, focusing on a traditional ballet repertoire. She moved to Los Angeles in 1979 and debuted her company as Bethune Ballet. By 1987 the company had evolved into Bethune Theatredanse, producing original multi-media performances often based on literature or film. Major productions included Mind’s Eye, Bird of Passage, Cradle of Fire, and Silent Roar.
Bethune endured a number of health problems from a young age, including scoliosis, lymphedema, and hip dysplasia. Determined to keep dancing, she underwent several surgeries and wore custom orthopedic tights the rest of her life in order to perform. Motivated by her own experience, she formed Dance Outreach, later known as Infinite Dreams, an arts education program for disabled children to learn and perform dance. Bethune and her staff taught classes and workshops throughout the Los Angeles area, and her students toured internationally and performed publicly at arts festivals and other venues, including the White House in 1989.
Zina Bethune was married to Sean Feeley for 42 years. She died in 2012 in an accident near Griffith Park in Los Angeles, when she stopped her car to help an injured animal. After her death, Infinite Dreams continued to hold classes and workshops under the name All-Abilities Dance until ceasing operations in 2015.
Scope and Content
Materials related to the history and operations of the Bethune Theatredanse dance company, and its arts education program Infinite Dreams, formerly known as Dance Outreach, both founded by Zina Bethune. Administrative series includes business records, promotional and publicity materials, programs, artist files, performance ideas, and participation in area events and festivals. Also includes some biographical information about founder Zina Bethune. Development and fundraising includes materials related to grants, benefits, outreach, and Bethune Theatredanse's involvement in the Los Angeles Theatre Center Cooperative. Production files consist of scripts, budgets, advertising, reviews, and other materials. Clippings document the activities of Zina Bethune, Bethune Theatredanse, and Dance Outreach. Photographs and audio-visual include Zina Bethune, Bethune Theatredanse dancers and productions, and Dance Outreach students and activities.
Organization and Arrangement
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1. Administrative
Series 2. Development and Fundraising
Series 3. Production Files
Series 4. Clippings
Series 5. Photographs
Series 6. Audio-Visual
Bethune, Zina; Dance teachers--Archives.; Dance therapy; Dance--California--Archives.
Container List
- Series 1: Administrative., 1979-2006.
  Scope and Content
  Materials related to the history and operations of Bethune Theatredanse and Dance Outreach, later known as Infinite Dreams. Includes promotional and publicity materials, programs, artist files, performance ideas, and participation in area events and festivals. Also includes some biographical information about founder Zina Bethune.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Use of electronic format material requires special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. To review these materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
  - Zina Bethune - biography., ca. 1980-2000. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Zina Bethune - resumes., 1980s-1990s. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Zina Bethune - appearances and speaking engagements., 1985-2001. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Zina Bethune - correspondence., undated. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Zina Bethune and Company - promotional materials., ca. 1979. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Zina Bethune and Company - programs., ca. 1980. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bethune Ballet - company profile., ca. 1982. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bethune Ballet - promotional materials., 1980-1987. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bethune Ballet - programs., 1980-1987. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bethune Ballet - logos and artwork., 1981. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bethune Ballet - events., 1982-1984. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bethune Ballet - Dance Lab proposal., ca. 1980s. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bethune Ballet - cloth banner., 1980s. (Box 58)
  - Company history and mission., 1980s-1990. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Promotional materials., 1990s-2000s. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Logos and artwork., 1994. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Graphics and artwork - CD-Rs., 2004 and undated. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Letterheads., 1980s-2000s. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Personnel and production lists., 1985, 1997-2001. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Newsletters., 1980-2002. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Press releases., 1983-1986. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Pressbook., 1980-2010. (Box 57, Folder 1-2)
  - Repertoire., 1995-1996. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Potential ballets - stories., ca. 1981-1982. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Potential ballets - notes and ideas., 1980s. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Potential ballets - stories., 1988. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Artist files., 1990-1996. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Student artwork., 1980s. (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Dance Outreach Fan Club booklet., 1990s. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Dance Outreach - information, promotional materials., 1995. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Dance Outreach - teachers., 1986-1987, 1995. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Dance Outreach - performances and appearances., 1988-2005. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Dance Outreach - student certificates., 1980s. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Dance Outreach - White House Visit., 1989. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Infinite Dreams - registration., ca. 2000s. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Los Angeles Dance Fair - registration and program., 1993. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - A Very Special Arts Festival - programs, flyers., 1984-1988, 2006. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Dance Pool - programs, flyers., 1990. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - LA Arts Open House - programs., 1995, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Other festivals and appearances - programs, flyers., 1985-2006. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Awards and commendations., 1985-2006. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Awards and commendations., 2001-2007. (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
  - Loan agreements., 1990. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Video waiver - Nutcracker., 1998. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Employment advertising., 1997. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Receipts., 1989-1990. (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Series 2: Development and Fundraising., 1984-2002.
  Documentation of fundraising efforts for Bethune Theatredanse and Dance Outreach, later known as Infinite Dreams. Includes grant applications and contracts, outreach to potential supporters, and materials related to various benefit events, particularly Dreams Come True, the annual Dance Outreach fundraiser. Also included are materials related to Bethnune Theatredanse's participation in the Los Angeles Theatre Center Cooperative in the early 1990s.
  - California Arts Council grant - contracts and invoices., 1994-1995. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - City of Los Angeles Cultural Grant program - applications., 1984-1986. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - City of Los Angeles Cultural Grant program - contracts and invoices., 1986-1987. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - City of Los Angeles Cultural Grant program - contracts and invoices., 1987-1988. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - City of Los Angeles Cultural Grant program - contracts and invoices., 1988-1989. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - City of Los Angeles Cultural Grant program - contracts and invoices., 1989-1990. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - County of Los Angeles grants - applications., 1985-1989. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - National State County grant - application., 1989. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Los Angeles Theatre Center Cooperative - agendas and meeting minutes., 1992-1993. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Los Angeles Theatre Center cooperative - correspondence., 1992-1993. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Los Angeles Theatre Center cooperative - background., 1992. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Los Angeles Theatre Center cooperative - proposal., 1992. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Thank-you letters., 1988-1990. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Letters of support - celebrity., 1980-1981. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Letters of support., 1988-1991. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - La Cage aux Folles au Ballet: Salute to Bethune Ballet - invitations., 1983-1984. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Dreams Come True - programs., 1984-1988. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Dreams Come True - press., 1989-1990. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Dreams Come True - supporter packets., 1990. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Dreams Come True - venue contract., 1990. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Dreams Come True - celebrity response., 1986-1989. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Dreams Come True - celebrity response., 1990. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Dreams Come True - planning., 1989-1990. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Friendraiser benefit - artwork., 2000. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Other benefits - invitations and advertising., 1984-2002. (Box 58, Folder 1, Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising - Righteous Persons/Spielberg., 1994. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising - Shambala/Tippi Hedren., 1995. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising - Paramount Studios., 1994. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising - Sony., 1994. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Fundraising - Harpo Productions - Kate Forte., 1997. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising - correspondence., 1984 and undated. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Charity events - invitations and correspondence., 1997. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Mailing lists - donors., 1991-1995. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Mailing lists - dance schools., 1990s. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Mailing lists - floppy discs., 1997. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Mailing lists - computer printouts., 1991-1992. (Box 55-56)
- Series 3: Production Files., 1987-2012.
  Materials related to Bethune Theatredanse productions, particularly Bird of Passage and Cradle of Fire. Includes scripts, contracts, casting information, budgets and expenses, advertising, artwork, reviews, and other documentation. Also scattered materials for Galileo, Jupiter, Apollo, Silent Roar, Tipperary, and other productions.
  - Subseries 1: Bird of Passage., 1989-1990.
    - Outline/synopsis., 1989-1990. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Script - first draft., 1989. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Script - second draft., 1990. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Script - third draft., 1990. (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Audition flyers., 1990. (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Cast., 1989. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Contracts and performers., 1989-1990. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Staff bios., ca. 1989. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Artwork., 1990. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Set design - drawings., ca. 1990. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Budget., 1989-1990. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Receipts., 1990. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Requests for support., 1989. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence from Robin McKee., 1990. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Copyrights., 1989. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Coronet Theatre agreement., 1990. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Press releases., 1990. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Schedules., 1989. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Artistic inspiration., undated. (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Outreach correspondence., 1990. (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Reviews., 1990. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 2: Cradle of Fire., 1988-1995.
    - Original video production contract., 1988. (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Synopsis/outline., 1993. (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - First draft - manuscript., 1993. (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - First draft., 1993. (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Second draft., 1993. (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Third draft., 1993. (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Text translations., 1993. (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Copyrights., 1994. (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Video treatment., 1995-1996. (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Casting submissions., 1993. (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Cast., 1993. (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Cast letters., 1994. (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Staff biographies., 1993. (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Press releases., 1993. (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Program artwork by Nova Graphic - floppy disc., 1993-1994. (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Program revisions., 1993. (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Advertising and contacts list., 1993. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Relevant articles., 1994. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - CNN library tape sales., 1993. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Technical requirements., 1993. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - American Film Institute grant application., 1994. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Box office., 1993. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Receipts., 1993. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Final expense report., 1994. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Budgets., 1994-1995. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Pepperdine performance cancellation., 1993. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Program artwork - Ken Lowell., 1993. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Contracts - staff., 1993. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Contracts - music and composition., 1993. (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Contracts - performers., 1993. (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Contracts - performers (Pepperdine shows)., 1993. (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Contracts - Pepperdine rental., 1993. (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Contact sheets - staff and cast., 1993. (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Audition flyers., 1993. (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Insurance., 1993. (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Thank you letters., 1993-1994. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Requests for support., 1993-1995. (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Los Angeles Theatre Center - grant narrative., 1995. (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Outreach correspondence., 1993-1994. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Poster., 1994. (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Posters, posted., 1993. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Advertising and flyers., 1993. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Press and reviews., 1993. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 3: Other productions., 1986-2012.
    - Frost and Fire - casting., 2002. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Frost and Fire - advertising and artwork., 2002. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Frost and Fire - flyer graphics and photos., 2007 and undated. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Frost and Fire - press release and information., 2002. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Frost and Fire - poster., 2002. (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Galileo, Jupiter, Apollo - promotional materials., 1995. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Galileo, Jupiter, Apollo - reviews., 1995. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Manvantara - promotional materials., 1996. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - The Manvantara Game - program., 1998. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Mind's Eye - program., 1987-1988. (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Mind's Eye - promotional materials., 1987-1988. (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Mind's Eye - contracts., 1991. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Sci-Fi Trilogy - story adaptations., ca. 1990s. (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Silent Roar - auditions., 2009. (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Silent Roar - poster., 2011. (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Silent Roar - original artwork poster on Syquest and Zip disc., undated. (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Silent Roar - promotional materials., 2009. (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Silent Roar - notebook., 2011. (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Silent Roar - reviews., 1997. (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Tipperary - casting., 1990. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Tipperary - budget., 1990. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Tipperary - script., 1990. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Tipperary - correspondence - Dunaira Holding., 1990. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Tipperary - staff and crew lists., 1990. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Tipperary - contracts with Dunaira Holding., 1990. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Tipperary - notes, schedules, issues., 1990. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - The Trial of St. Joan - synopsis., 1986. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - The Trial of St. Joan - artwork by Kathy Jacobi., 1986. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - The Trial of St. Joan - reviews., 1986. (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Series 4: Clippings., 1979-2007.
  Newspaper clippings from a variety of Southern California sources documenting the activities of Zina Bethune, Bethune Theatredanse, and particularly Dance Outreach, later known as Infinite Dreams.
  - Zina Bethune miscellaneous., 1979-1992. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Dance Magazine - "The Magic of Clara"., 1984. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Verdugo Newspaper Group - A Special Art., 1984. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Dance Outreach/Dreams Come True miscellaneous., 1984-1993. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Los Angeles Times - "Dance Outreach Gives the Disabled a Leg Up"., 1985. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Los Angeles Times - Brown Bag Goes Highbrow., 1985. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Los Angeles Herald Examiner - "The Trial of Saint Joan: This Choreographer Almost Lived It"., 1985. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Glendale Today - "Zina Bethune Reaches Out With Dance"., 1985. (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - The Hollywood Reporter: Off the Cuff., 1986. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Drama-Logue - "Dance Outreach Program Continues"., 1986. (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Los Angeles Times - Dance Outreach at Roxy., 1986. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Childrens' Series to Feature Ballet., 1986. (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - The Hollywood Reporter - Rambling Reporter., 1986. (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Los Angeles Times - "Arts Festival Gives Kids a Day to Shine"., 1986. (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Going Hollywood - Dance Outreach., 1986. (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Tinseltown Go Round., 1986. (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Beverly Hills [213] - Dreams Come True., 1986. (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Movieline - Don't Let Me Lose This Dream., 1986. (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Variety - "Dance Outreach to Benefit From Dreams Fundraiser"., 1986. (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - L.A. Life - "Dance Outreach Benefit Reaches Out to Help Handicapped Youngsters"., 1987. (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - The Enterprise - "Dance, Video Share Palace Stage"., 1987. (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Star News "Taking It One Big Step at a Time"., 1987. (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Dance Teacher Now - "Zina Bethune: A Special Kind of Teaching"., 1987. (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Inside Hollywood with David Galligan., 1987. (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Press-Telegram - "Dancing For Joy"., 1987. (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Daily News - "Sidelined Dancer Shares Her Gift with Children"., 1987. (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Daily Breeze - "Dance Outreach: Helping Kids Break Through Handicaps"., 1987. (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Variety - "Dance is Common Language in Outreach's Trip to China., 1988. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Camarillo Daily News - "Ballet to Perform for Local Student"., 1988. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Time of Your Life - "Dance Outreach Welcomes Seniors, Special Children"., 1989. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles Times "When Dreams Come True at the Century Plaza"., 1989. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Daily News - "Cooking Up Benefit for Kicking Up Heels"., 1989. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Daily News - "Benefit Staged to Help Disabled Children Dance"., 1989. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Los Angeles Times - "For the Young Disabled, Studying Dance Can Be a Saving Grace"., 1989. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - The Daily Report - "Allowing the Heart to Keep Dancing Despite Physical Hardships., 1989. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Los Angeles Times - Valley Scene., 1989. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - China Reconstructs - "Zina Bethune: Teaching Disabled Children to Dance"., 1989. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Senior World of Los Angeles County - "Dance Class Emphasizes Ability"., 1989. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Variety - "Dance Outreach in the People's Republic of China"., 1989. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Variety - Bethune Theatredanse thank you for "From the Heart"., 1989. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - The Hollywood Reporter - "TV Review: From the Heart"., 1989. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Variety - "Bethune TV Special Will Air on Sunday"., 1989. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Beverly Hills [213] - "Dreams Come True Gala"., 1989. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Zina Bethune - Grand Hotel performance., 1991. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Daily News - LA Life: Adventurous Symbion Launches Multimedia Barrage., 1990. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Press Telegram - "Baretta Softened by Kids at Dance"., 1991. (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - New York Newsday - "Doctors and Desire Put Her On Her Toes"., 1991. (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Los Angeles Times - "Dance Puts Children On Their Toes"., 1991. (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Anaheim Bulletin - "Disabled Dancers Learn By Doing"., 1991. (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Independent - "Broadway Dancer Brings Smiles to Hope"., 1991. (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - The Buena Park News - "Students Escape Through Dance"., 1991. (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - The Orange County Register - "A Chance to Dance and Prance"., 1991. (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - The Orange County Register - "Circus Party Benefits Dancers"., 1992. (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - "Dancing as Fast as I Can"., 1992. (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Woman's Own - "Disabled Ballerina Teaches Handicapped Kids to Dance"., 1992. (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Los Angeles Times - "Benefit Under Big Top Aids Dance Outreach"., 1992. (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Daily News - "High Stepping Goes High-Tech., 1992. (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Daily Pilot - "Everyone at Village Crean Loves a Circus"., 1992. (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - New Age Journal - "The Dancer Within"., 1992. (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - The Orange County Register - "Big-Top Event Helps Keep Kids Dancing"., 1993. (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - The Orange County Register - "Dancing as Fast as They Can"., 1993. (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Family Circle - "Women Who Make a Difference"., 1994. (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Hip Parade - "Participation is the Criteria"., 1994. (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Los Angeles Times - "Who's That Knocking At My Door"., 1995. (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - San Gabriel Valley Weekly - "Tapping a Vast Potential"., 1996. (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Los Angeles Times - "Nonprofits Win Disney Cash Prizes"., 1996. (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Burbank Leader - "Women Who Make a Difference"., 1997. (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - The Orange County Register - "Inspired Footsteps"., 1997. (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Burbank Leader - "Theatredanse Productions Shine to Create a Future"., 1997. (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Los Angeles Times - "Congratulations to the LA Times Regional Award Winners., 1998. (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Los Angeles Times - Nutcracker press., 1998. (Box 9, Folder 44)